Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - R
        - Ranking, Copper - Friends, 1989; SR-23579; Ranking, Copper; Lee, Johnny (Box 405)
          Blue Mountain Records
        - Ranking Dread - Gate man, 1983; SR-23580; Ranking Dread (Box 405)
          Catalog # BMBIS 7; A-side Matrix # BM DIS-7-A-1
          Body Music
        - Ranking Dread - Kunte Kinte Roots, 1979; SR-23581; Ranking Dread (Box 405)
          Catalog # BS 1037; A-side Matrix # BS-1037-A-1
          Burning Sounds
        - Ranking Joe - Armageddon, 1982; SR-23582; Ranking Joe (Box 405)
          Catalog # KVL 9010; A-side Matrix # KVL-9010-A
          Kingdom Records
        - Rankin, Louie - The typewriter EP, 1993; SR-23583; Rankin, Louie (Box 405)
          Catalog # XLT 41; A-side Matrix # XLT-41 A
          XL Recordings
        - Ranking, Louie - The typewriter, 1991; SR-23584; Ranking, Louie (Box 405)
          Catalog # SRD 42; A-side Matrix # SRD42A
          Shelly's Records
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Ranking, Louie - The typewriter, 1991; SR-23585; Ranking, Louie (Box 405)
        - Ranking, Louie - Divert; Version, 1990; SR-23586; Ranking, Louie (Box 405)
          No Discogs entry
          Catalog # CC-002; A-side Matrix # CC00-2-A
          C.O.C. Records
        - Peter Ranking & General Lucky - Easies & squeezies; You I love, 1981; SR-23587; Peter Ranking & General Lucky; Papa Lucky (Box 405)
          Catalog # VPRD 76; A-side Matrix # VPRD 76-A
          Jah Guidance
          Jamaica
        - Ranking, Peter - Jah standing over me, 1982; SR-23588; Ranking, Peter; General Lucky (Box 405)
          Catalog # SCLP 011; A-side Matrix # SCLP 011 A
          Silver Camel
        - Ranking, Peter - Beverley Black, 1982; SR-23589; Ranking, Peter; General Lucky (Box 405)
          Catalog # GRED 98; A-side Matrix # GRED98 A
          Greensleeves Records
        - Ranking, Rodney - Police brutality, 1993; SR-23590; Ranking, Rodney (Box 405)
          Catalog # JBR-001; A-side Matrix # JBR 001A
          Josey Boy Records
          Bronx, New York
        - Ranking Slackness - Slackest LP, 1979; SR-23591; Ranking Slackness (Box 405)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # DMLP-1080-A
          Techniques
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Ranks, Cutty - A who seh me dun, 1992; SR-23592; Ranks, Cutty (Box 405)
          Catalog # VPRT-001; A-side Matrix # VPRT 001-A
          VP Records
          Jamaica, New York
        - Ranks, Cutty - From mi heart, 1992; SR-23593; Ranks, Cutty; Funkmaster Flex (Box 405)
          Catalog # SHANACHIE 45001; A-side Matrix # SH-45001-A
          Shanachie
          Newton, New Jersey
        - Ranks, Cutty - Limb by limb, 1993; SR-23594; Ranks, Cutty (Box 405)
          Catalog # FAD 108; A-side Matrix # FAD 108-A
          Fashion Records
        - Ranks, Cutty - Dis a victory; Work a pay off, 1993; SR-23595; Ranks, Cutty; Rebel, Tony (Box 405)
          Catalog # VPRD-827; A-side Matrix # VPRD-827-A
          Star Trail
        - Ranks, Cutty - Limb by limb, 1993; SR-23596; Ranks, Cutty (Box 405)
          Catalog # VPRD 6341; A-side Matrix # VPRD-6341-A
        - Ranks, Cutty - Hustle hustle, 1994; SR-23597; Ranks, Cutty (Box 405)
          Catalog # PRO-7417-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7417 A
        - Ranks, Cutty - Living condition (Bobby Konders hip-hop remixes), 1992; SR-23598; Ranks, Cutty; Funkmaster Flex (Box 405)
          Catalog # SH 7032; A-side Matrix # SH-7032-A
        - Ranks, Koolie - Roughneck, 1985; SR-23599; Ranks, Koolie (Box 405)
          Catalog # BR 3473; A-side Matrix # BR-3473A
          Bravel Records
        - Ranks, Nardo - Burrup, 1990; SR-23600; Ranks, Nardo (Box 405)
          Catalog # VPRD-587; A-side Matrix # VPRD-587-A
          Gold Disc
        - Ranks, Nardo - Fighty fighty; Fighty dub, 1990; SR-23601; Ranks, Nardo; Dennis the Menace (Box 405)
          Catalog # TY-03; A-side Matrix # TY-03-A
          Tan-Yah
          Staten Island, New York
        - Ranks, Nardo - Burrup, 1990; SR-23602; Ranks, Nardo (Box 405)
          Catalog # PRO-7316-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7316-A
        - Ranks, Nardo - New Jersey drive, 1991; SR-23603; Ranks, Nardo; Demus, Junior (Box 405)
          Catalog # PRO-7335; A-side Matrix # PRO-7335-A-RE2
        - Ranks, Nardo - Rough Nardo Ranking, 1992; SR-23604; Ranks, Nardo (Box 405)
          Catalog # PRO-1417; A-side Matrix # PRO-1417-A
        - Ranks, Nardo - Baby don't stop can't stop won't stop, 2003; SR-23605; Ranks, Nardo (Box 405)
          Catalog # #RIPWBSRNWBJR; A-side Matrix # RIPWBSRNWBJR-A
          Satori Productions
        - Ranks, Peter - Kiss my!!, 1991; SR-23606; Ranks, Peter; Lloydie Crucial (Box 405)
          Catalog # RADZ 3 DJ; A-side Matrix # RADZ 3 A-1U-1-1
          Raiders Records
        - Ranks, Shabba - Wicked in bed, 1989; SR-23607; Ranks, Shabba (Box 405)
          Catalog # VPRD-487; A-side Matrix # VPRD-487-A
          Digital-B
        - Ranks, Shabba - Roots and culture; Write mi will, 1990; SR-23608; Ranks, Shabba; Rickey Stereo (Box 405)
          In same jacket as # SR-23609. Different discs.
          Catalog # VPRD-567; A-side Matrix # VPRD-567-A
        - Ranks, Shabba - Gal yuh good, 1990; SR-23609; Ranks, Shabba (Box 405)
          In same jacket as # SR-23608. Different discs.
          Catalog # VPRD-643; A-side Matrix # VPRD-643-A
        - Ranks, Shabba - Let's get it on, 1994; SR-23610; Ranks, Shabba (Box 405)
          Catalog # EAS 6684; A-side Matrix # XSS-6684-A-1A
        - Ranks, Shabba - Slow and sexy, 1992; SR-23611; Ranks, Shabba; Gill, Johnny (Box 405)
          Catalog # 49 74742; A-side Matrix # XSS 74742 A
        - Ranks, Shabba - Muscle grip, 1992; SR-23612; Ranks, Shabba (Box 405)
          Catalog # 49 74806; A-side Matrix # XSS 74806 A
        - Ranks, Shabba - Fanciness, 1994; SR-23613; Ranks, Shabba; Lady G (Box 405)
          Catalog # HAL 12533; A-side Matrix # HAL 12533-A BHOTMASTERING
          Radikal Records
          Miami, Florida
        - Ranks, Shabba - Caan dun, 1990; SR-23614; Ranks, Shabba (Box 405)
          Catalog # VPRD-667; A-side Matrix # VPRD-667-A Caan Dun Shabba Ranks
          Steely and Clevie Records
        - Ranks, Shabba - Shine eye gal, 1995; SR-23615; Ranks, Shabba; Rose, Mykal (Box 405)
          Catalog # EAS 7095; A-side Matrix # EAS-7095-A EHFM'95
        - Ranks, Shabba - Let's get it on, 1994; SR-23616; Ranks, Shabba (Box 405)
          Catalog # EAS 6684; A-side Matrix # XSS-6684A-1AS CSB
        - Ranks, Shabba - Muscle grip, 1992; SR-23617; Ranks, Shabba (Box 405)
          Catalog # 49 74806; A-side Matrix # XSS 74806A CSB
        - Ranks, Shabba - Bedroom bully, 1992; SR-23618; Ranks, Shabba (Box 405)
          Catalog # EAS 05030; A-side Matrix # XSS 5030A CSB
        - Ranks, Shabba - Hood top, 1991; SR-23619; Ranks, Shabba (Box 405)
          Catalog # Digital-1; A-side Matrix # Digital-1-A
        - Ranks, Shabba - Housecall, 1991; SR-23620; Ranks, Shabba; Priest, Maxi (Box 405)
          Catalog # 657347 6; A-side Matrix # 31-657347-20-1A-1
        - Ranks, Shabba - Ram dancehall, 1994; SR-23621; Ranks, Shabba (Box 405)
          Catalog # EAS 6227; A-side Matrix # XSS-6227-A-1A CSB
        - Ranks, Shabba - Roots and culture, 1995; SR-23622; Ranks, Shabba; Exzactly (Box 405)
          Catalog # VPRD 5836; A-side Matrix # VPRD 5836A Roots&Culture Remix
        - Ranks, Sluggy - Ghetto youth bust, 1994; SR-23623; Ranks, Sluggy (Box 405)
          Catalog # PRO-1457 DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-1457-1A AATB
        - Ranks, Sluggy - Ghetto youth bust, 1994; SR-23624; Ranks, Sluggy (Box 405)
          Catalog # PRO-7427-0-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7427-0A AATB
        - Ranks, Squidly - Fall in love; Maga man, 1993; SR-23625; Ranks, Squidly; Queen Paula (Box 405)
          Catalog # VPRD-5115-AA; A-side Matrix # VPRD-5115-AA MAGA MAN
          Stone Love
        - Randi Rann - Cars, 1988; SR-23626; Randi Rann (Box 405)
          Catalog # AVE 8500; A-side Matrix # AVE-8500 A G1A G1 A8
          Avenue Records
          Memphis, Tennessee
        - Randi Rann - Cars, 1989; SR-23627; Randi Rann (Box 405)
          Catalog # AVE 8501; A-side Matrix # AVE-8500 A G1A G1 A9
        - Ransom, Linda - Na na hey hey kiss her goodbye, 1983; SR-23628; Ransom, Linda (Box 405)
          Catalog # MK-002; A-side Matrix # S-10448-MK-002-A-
          Marrakech Records
        - Ransom, Tony - Stay if you wanna, 1985; SR-23629; Ransom, Tony (Box 405)
          In same jacket as # SR-23630. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # ER-1285; A-side Matrix # ER-1285-A-1-1-1-Q-3 PRC
          Expansion Records
        - Ransom, Tony - Stay if you wanna, 1985; SR-23630; Ransom, Tony (Box 405)
          In same jacket as # SR-23629. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # ER-1285; A-side Matrix # ER-1285-A-1-1-1-Q PRC 116-616-5
        - Ranx, Shawnie - Boomin body, 1995; SR-23631; Ranx, Shawnie; Ranks, Shawnie (Box 406)
          Catalog # 25039-1; A-side Matrix # 25039-1-A
          Select Records
        - Ranx, Shawnie - Boomin body, 1995; SR-23632; Ranx, Shawnie; Ranks, Shawnie (Box 406)
        - Ranx, Shawnie - Boomin body, 1995; SR-23633; Ranx, Shawnie; Ranks, Shawnie (Box 406)
        - Ranx, Shawnie - Goody good love, 1996; SR-23634; Ranx, Shawnie; Ranks, Shawnie (Box 406)
          Promo. No Discogs entry.
          Catalog # PRO 57; A-side Matrix # PRO-57-A
        - Rap-O-Matic, Ltd. - Lies, lies, 1986; SR-23635; Rap-O-Matic, Ltd. (Box 406)
          Catalog # PRO-7098-DJ; A-side Matrix # A-PRO-7098-A
        - Rapination - Love me the right way (the Danny Tenaglia remixes), 1993; SR-23636; Rapination; Rapino Brothers (Box 406)
          Promo (says promo on discogs but not on album)
          Catalog # RDAB 62529-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-62529-1-A1
          RCA
        - Rapologists - Hip hop beat, 1984; SR-23637; Rapologists; Flakey C (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23638. 2 copies.
          Catalog # WHIZ 1; A-side Matrix # WHIZ-1-A-1 NOEL
          Billy Boy Records
        - Rapologists - Hip hop beat, 1984; SR-23638; Rapologists; Flakey C (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23637. 2 copies.
        - Rappagariya - It’s a showtime, 2001; SR-23639; Rappagariya (Box 406)
          Catalog # VICL-35248; A-side Matrix # SOML-0022-A S-46487
          Happy House
          Japan
        - Rappers' Convention - Rappers' convention, 1986; SR-23640; Rappers' Convention (Box 406)
          Catalog # ST-17225; A-side Matrix # ST-1-17225-Z4
          EMI America
        - Rappers' Convention - Stupid fresh, 1986; SR-23641; Rappers' Convention (Box 406)
          Catalog # SPRO-9933; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9933-P2 B-26109-P2 15025 1-1
        - Rappers' Convention - Stupid fresh, 1986; SR-23642; Rappers' Convention (Box 406)
        - Rappers Rapp Group - Rappers rapp theme, 1982; SR-23643; Rappers Rapp Group (Box 406)
          Catalog # 12"-RR-1990; A-side Matrix # RR 1990-A
          Rappers Rapp Disco Co.
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Ain't no playa like…, 1996; SR-23644; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23645. Different Discs.
          Catalog # Y-58527; A-side Matrix # Y-58527-1-A
          Chrysalis
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Ain't no playa, 1995; SR-23645; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23644. Different Discs.
          Catalog # SPRO-10459; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10459-1-A
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - A lil' some'em some'em, 1996; SR-23646; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
          Catalog # SPRO-10497; A-side Matrix # 7087-6-10497-1-8-A-1
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Off parole, 1996; SR-23647; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
          Catalog # S-33233; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10499-7087-6-10499 A
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Off parole, 1996; SR-23648; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Playaz club (the remixes), 1994; SR-23649; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
          Catalog # SPRO-19954; A-side Matrix # SPRO-19954-A
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Playaz club (the remixes), 1994; SR-23650; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Playaz club (the remixes), 1994; SR-23651; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Playaz club (the remixes), 1994; SR-23652; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Ain't no playa, 1995; SR-23653; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Off parole (disc one), 1996; SR-23654; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23655. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # SPRO-10487; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10487-A2
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Off parole (disc two), 1996; SR-23655; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23654. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # SPRO-10487; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10487-C
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Off parole (disc one), 1996; SR-23656; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23657. Double album.Promo
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - Off parole (disc two), 1996; SR-23657; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23656. Double album.Promo
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - I'll be around; Just 'cause I call you a bitch (disc one), 1994; SR-23658; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23659. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # SPRO-19966; A-side Matrix # SPRO-19966-A
        - Rappin' 4-Tay - I'll be around; just 'cause I call you a bitch (disc two), 1994; SR-23659; Rappin' 4-Tay (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23658. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # SPRO-19966; A-side Matrix # SPRO-19966-1-C-RE1
        - Rappin' Duke - Que pasa?, 1985; SR-23660; Rappin' Duke (Box 406)
          Catalog # JWP LP 6969; A-side Matrix # J.W.P. LP-6969-A
          JWP Records
        - Rappin' Duke - Buzzy bragg, 1986; SR-23661; Rappin' Duke; Rappin' Duke & Friends; Morabito, D. (Box 406)
          Catalog # TJ 1000; A-side Matrix # TJ 1000 A
          Toe Jam Records
          Hillside, New Jersey
        - Rappin' Duke - Duke is back, 1986; SR-23662; Rappin' Duke (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23663. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # TB 881; A-side Matrix # HERBIE JR TB-881-A
          Tommy Boy
        - Rappin' Duke - Duke is back, 1986; SR-23663; Rappin' Duke (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23662. 2 copies.Promo
        - Rappin' Duke - Duke is back, 1986; SR-23664; Rappin' Duke (Box 406)
        - Rappin' Lords - Bad self, 1986; SR-23665; Rappin' Lords (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23666. 2 copies.
          Catalog # HOT 1; A-side Matrix # Hot-1-A "Prince Sincere, Forever Love, Q, Ron, Dawn All Hit Bound"
          Hot Records
          Fort Lauderdale, Florida
        - Rappin' Lords - Bad self, 1986; SR-23666; Rappin' Lords (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23665. 2 copies.
        - Rappin' Lords - Bad self, 1986; SR-23667; Rappin' Lords (Box 406)
        - Rare Bird - As your mind flies by, 1970; SR-23668; Rare Bird (Box 406)
          Catalog # ABCS-716; A-side Matrix # ABCS-716-A
          ABC Records
        - Rare Earth - Get ready, 1969; SR-23669; Rare Earth (Box 406)
          Catalog # RS 507; A-side Matrix # X4RS-4134-1 C HS-1634
          Motown Records
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Rare Essence - Live at Celebrity Hall; Live at the Metro Club, 1987; SR-23670; Rare Essence (Box 406)
          Catalog # RE-610; A-side Matrix # RE-610-A
          Sounds of the Capital
          Washington, D.C.
        - Rare Essence - Back up against the wall, 1983; SR-23671; Rare Essence (Box 406)
          Catalog # RE-607; A-side Matrix # RE-607-A
        - Rare Essence - Get your freak on (disc one), 1995; SR-23672; Rare Essence (Box 406)
          Catalog # RE 0315-1; A-side Matrix # RE-315-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 11567 B
        - Rare Essence - Give it here, 1986; SR-23673; Rare Essence (Box 406)
          Catalog # TDE 3019; A-side Matrix # TDE 3019-A
          T.T.E.D. Records
        - Rare Essence - We push (the remix), 1999; SR-23674; Rare Essence (Box 406)
          Test Pressing
          Catalog # RE 2013; A-side Matrix # RE-2013-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 43147 B 00-28-03 2-S
          Rare One Records
        - Rare Essence - Live in 2004, 2004; SR-23675; Rare Essence (Box 406)
          Catalog # RE-2005; A-side Matrix # RE-2005-A DON GROSSINGER
        - Rare Essence - We push, 1999; SR-23676; Rare Essence; Redman (Box 406)
          Catalog # RE-2012; A-side Matrix # RE-2012-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 39775 B 12-81-01 1-S
        - Rare Essence - Live at Club U, v2 (disc one), 2003; SR-23677; Rare Essence; Doug E. Fresh (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23678. Double album.
          Catalog # RE-2004; A-side Matrix # RE-2004-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 71186 DON GROSSINGER
        - Rare Essence - Live at Club U, v2 (disc two), 2003; SR-23678; Rare Essence; Doug E. Fresh (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23677. Double album.
          Catalog # RE-2004; A-side Matrix # RE-2004-1-C EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 71187 DON GROSSINGER
        - Rare Essence - We push, 1999; SR-23679; Rare Essence; Redman (Box 406)
          Catalog # RE-2012; A-side Matrix # RE-2012-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 39775 B 72-21-11 3-S
        - Rare Essence - Doin it old school style, Live at Club U (disc one), 2001; SR-23680; Rare Essence (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23681. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # RE-2002; A-side Matrix # RE-2002-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 49387 DON GROSSINGER
        - Rare Essence - Doin it old school style, Live at Club U (disc two), 2001; SR-23681; Rare Essence (Box 406)
          In same jacket as # SR-23680. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # RE-2002; A-side Matrix # RE-2002-1-C EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 49392 DON GROSSINGER
        - Rare Essence - Shoo-be-do-wop, 1984; SR-23682; Rare Essence (Box 406)
          Catalog # RE 608; A-side Matrix # RE-608-A
        - Rare Essence - Hey now, 1988; SR-23683; Rare Essence (Box 406)
          Catalog # IHY 1002; A-side Matrix # IHY-1002-A HUB masterdisk TD
          I Hear Ya! Records
        - Rare Essence - Give it here, 1986; SR-23684; Rare Essence (Box 406)
        - Rare Essence - Give it here, 1986; SR-23685; Rare Essence (Box 406)
        - Rare Essence - Work that thang, 2002; SR-23686; Rare Essence (Box 406)
          Catalog # RE2016; A-side Matrix # RE-2016-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 60572 DON GROSSINGER
        - Rare Essence - Shoo-be-do-wop, 1984; SR-23687; Rare Essence (Box 407)
          In same jacket as # SR-23688. 2 copies.
        - Rare Essence - Shoo-be-do-wop, 1984; SR-23688; Rare Essence (Box 407)
          In same jacket as # SR-23687. 2 copies.
        - Rare Essence - So what u want?, 1994; SR-23689; Rare Essence (Box 407)
          Catalog # RE500-12; A-side Matrix # RE-500-12-A
        - Rare Essence - Live pa #4 (back at the classics 04-07-02), 2001; SR-23690; Rare Essence (Box 407)
          Catalog # RE3004-1; A-side Matrix # RE-3004-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 63312 DON GROSSINGER
        - Rare Essence - Live pa #4 (back at the classics 04-07-02), 2001; SR-23691; Rare Essence (Box 407)
        - Rare Essence - Lock it, 1991; SR-23692; Rare Essence (Box 407)
          In same jacket as # SR-23693. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RE615-12; A-side Matrix # RE-615-A
        - Rare Essence - Lock it, 1991; SR-23693; Rare Essence (Box 407)
          In same jacket as # SR-23692. 2 copies.
        - Rare Essence - Flipside, 1986; SR-23694; Rare Essence (Box 407)
          Catalog # 884 319-1; A-side Matrix # 884-319-1-BS-ES
          Mercury Records
        - Rare Essence - Get your freak on, 1995; SR-23695; Rare Essence (Box 407)
          Dated as 1996 on Discogs
          Catalog # RE 0315-1; A-side Matrix # RE-315-1-C EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 11567 B
        - Rare Essence - The essence of Rare Essence, 1995; SR-23696; Rare Essence (Box 407)
          Catalog # RE320-1; A-side Matrix # RE-320-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 1268 B 12
        - Rare Essence - We push (the remix), 1999; SR-23697; Rare Essence (Box 407)
          Test Pressing. No Discogs entry
          Catalog # RE 2013; A-side Matrix # RE-2013-1-B EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 43147 B 00-85-3 S-S
        - Ras - Remain anonymous; Etc., 1994; SR-23698; Ras (Box 407)
          Catalog # PW 360; A-side Matrix # PW-360-A S-29168
          PatchWerk Recordings
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Ras Kass - Oral sex, 1999; SR-23699; Ras Kass (Box 407)
          Catalog # SPRO 81222; A-side Matrix # 81222-13-A S-41241 G-1 Dave
        - Ras Kass Of Western Hemisfear - Won't catch me runnin', 1994; SR-23700; Ras Kass Of Western Hemisfear (Box 407)
          Catalog # PW 360; A-side Matrix # PW-360-C RE-1 S-29742 REI
        - Ras Kass - Anything goes; On earth as it is, 1996; SR-23701; Ras Kass (Box 407)
          Catalog # SPRO 50913; A-side Matrix # S-33478 PVL-53219-A
        - Ras Kass - Anything goes; On earth as it is, 1996; SR-23702; Ras Kass (Box 407)
        - Ras Kass - H₂0proof, 1998; SR-23703; Ras Kass (Box 407)
          Catalog # SPRO 81079; A-side Matrix # SPRO-81079-A F-1 S-38647 Dave
        - Ras Kass - Live from C-Arson, 1996; SR-23704; Ras Kass; D.J. Nasty (Box 407)
          Catalog # SPRO 30101; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30101-A G1 RM S-34146
        - Ras Kass - Live from C-Arson, 1996; SR-23705; Ras Kass; D.J. Nasty (Box 407)
        - Ras Kass - Soul on ice (clean), 1996; SR-23706; Ras Kass (Box 407)
          Catalog # SPRO 30111; A-side Matrix # S-34518 SPRO-30111A G1 RM
        - Ras Kass - Soul on ice (clean), 1996; SR-23707; Ras Kass (Box 407)
        - Ras Kass - Rasassination; It is what it is, 1998; SR-23708; Ras Kass (Box 407)
          Catalog # SPRO 81135; A-side Matrix # SPRO-81135-A S-39923 G-1 Dave
        - Ras Kass - Ghetto fabulous; H₂0proof, 1998; SR-23709; Ras Kass; Dr. Dre (Box 407)
          Catalog # PVL 53453; A-side Matrix # PVL-53453-A S-39024 F-1
        - Ras Kass - Soul on ice (remix); Marinatin', 1996; SR-23710; Ras Kass (Box 407)
          Catalog # PVL 53258; A-side Matrix # PVL-53258-A G1 RM S-34474
        - Ras Kass - Soul on ice (disc one), 1996; SR-23711; Ras Kass (Box 407)
          In same jacket as # SR-23712. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 50529; A-side Matrix # 50529-A KR S-34000 REI
        - Ras Kass - Soul on ice (disc two), 1996; SR-23712; Ras Kass (Box 407)
          In same jacket as # SR-23711. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 50529; A-side Matrix # 50529-C KR S-34002 REI
        - Ras Kass - Anything goes; On earth as it is, 1996; SR-23713; Ras Kass (Box 407)
          In same jacket as # SR-23714. Different discs.Promo
        - Funk Daddy - Tha source, 1995; SR-23714; Funk Daddy (Box 407)
          In same jacket as # SR-23713. Different discs.
          Catalog # 10019-1; A-side Matrix # 10019-1-A S-31870
          Till Ya Tight Records
        - Rasa - Everything you see is me, 1978; SR-23715; Rasa (Box 407)
          Catalog # RA-106; A-side Matrix # RA 106A
          Govinda Records
        - Rascal & Klone - Zero tolerance; Terminal velocity, 2002; SR-23716; Rascal & Klone (Box 407)
          Catalog # SHAKE003; A-side Matrix # SHAKE 003A TOLERANCE
          Shakedown
        - Rascals - Rock and roll treasures (Disc one), 1985; SR-23717; Rascals (Box 407)
          In same jacket as # SR-23718. Double album.
          Catalog # PDL 2-1106; A-side Matrix # OP 2706-1A-A 1-1
          Warner Special Productions
          Passaic, New Jersey
        - Rascals - Rock and roll treasures (Disc two), 1985; SR-23718; Rascals (Box 407)
          In same jacket as # SR-23717. Double album.
          Catalog # PDL 2-1106; A-side Matrix # OP 2706-2AB -1
        - Rasco - Thin line; Gunz still hot (remix), 2001; SR-23719; Rasco (Box 407)
          Catalog # COPA021; A-side Matrix # 5344-COPA021-1 (A) S-46610